## SEUNGGI LEE

## Front-End Web Developer



## **CONTACT ME AT:**

Phone number: (289) 440-4090 Email: seunggi.lee21@gmail.com Portfolio: <u>seunggilee.com</u>

Github: <u>Leaden132</u> Linkedin: <u>Seunggi Lee</u>

### **EDUCATION**

# Web Development Immersive Bootcamp

Juno College of Technology, 2021

- Immersive Web Development Bootcamp
- · Accelerated JavaScript
- Accelerated Web Development

### Master of Science (MSc) in Physiology

University of Toronto, 2017-2020

#### **BSc Honours Biology**

McMaster University, 2012-2016

### **SKILLS**

- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
- JavaScript (ES6), JQuery
- React, TypeScript
- Responsive design, Accessibility
- REST/GraphQL APIs, Firebase
- Redux, Contentful (CMS)
- · Basic understanding of Node.js
- · Version Control & GitHub
- PSD conversion
- Scope Management
- · Paired / Mob Programming
- · Strong communication skills
- · Highly adaptive
- Complex problem solving
- Fast learner
- Attention to detail
- · Project Leadership

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a front-end web developer with a background in **neuroscience** research and I am proficient at up-to-date industry standard **HTML5**, **CSS3** and **JavaScript** and popular modern libraries like **React** to build highly **accessible** and **responsive** websites.

Through 5+ years of research lab experience, I am extremely familiar with working on challenging problems while being on tight deadlines and come up with the result collaborating with diverse teams.

### FEATURED PROJECTS

# League Matches (<u>Live</u> | <u>Git</u>) - React | TypeScript | REST API | AWS Lambda | Node.js | CSS3 | HTML5

- League of Legends match history search / analytics website built with react router utilizing extensive Riot API
- · Can search within 120 million userbase
- Created my own API proxy integration with AWS Lambda Function to bypass CORS policy

# Not-So-Trivial-Pursuit (<u>Live</u> | <u>Git</u>) - React | REST API | Firebase | Sass | HTML5

- Trivia quiz built with React that displays randomly selected questions while tracking scores and quiz progress
- Stores user information with unique ID and let the returning user keep playing from saved progress point
- Git collaborative project where I led and made decisions on user experience, development workflow and core logics

#### **EXPERIENCES**

#### Mentor

Juno College of Technology, 2021-present

 Assisted in teaching HTML and CSS to a large group of students by debugging websites, building apps and providing one-on-one guidance and support

#### **Research Assistant**

Krembil Research Institute Neuroscience Division, 2017-2020

- Worked on several neuroscience research projects to develop treatments for diseases related with Blood-Brain-Barrier integrity loss.
- Designed and carried out delicate experiments and analyzed critical data obtained under very tight deadlines by positively engaging with lab members.
- Contributed to a national neuroscience conference (CAN/ACN) to present on the role of Hfe2 (hemojuvelin) in maintaining Blood-Brain-Barrier integrity